{
    "id": "2bcb04ea207b4f7ba37cae9c8ce9ca66",
    "title": "Active And Passive Voice Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The parcels have ………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sent",
                "been sent",
                "been sending"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She ……………….. the report.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is preparing",
                "is being prepared",
                "is prepared"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The seeds have not …………………. yet.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "been germinating",
                "germinated",
                "germinating"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The meal ………………… at 12 pm.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "served",
                "was serving",
                "was served"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The hostess ………………… everyone with open arms.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "receiving",
                "received",
                "was received",
                "has receiving"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The child ...................... since Monday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has missing",
                "has missed",
                "has been missing"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The children ……………….. a ruckus.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "created",
                "was created",
                "was being created"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The boys have ………………… in their assignments.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "been handing",
                "been handed",
                "handed"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The mother ………………… her son against working too hard.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "advised",
                "advising",
                "has been advised"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………. to quit smoking.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "told",
                "was told",
                "has told"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}